Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/h101 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

graphRAG

Digital human, ER-Nerf, Nerf, ... Text-to-Speech

Certifications

Neural Networks and Deep Learning Neo4j Certified Professional

Honors-Awards

Third prize in the P-Start up competition 2022.

First prize of Al challenge PTIT 2023.

Top 22 DENSO FACTORY HACKS

Top 24 GDSC Hackathon Việt Nam 2022

Consolation prize in ICPC PTIT competition 2022,2023.

Nguyen Hung

-- Al Engineer--

Phường Khương Đình, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

I am a senior student at PTIT.

I have been studying and researching AI at Naver lab PTIT and IEC PTIT.

During my studies at PTIT, I participated in many competitions both inside and outside the Institute. Therefore, I have experience in many fields of AI: CV, NLP, RL,... My experience is mainly in CV, and currently, I am working with digital humans and have some experience with RAG, GraphRAG, Langgraph.

Contact:

_Phone Number: 0399284295.

_Gmail: hungnm1.work@gmail.com.

_Facebook : https://www.facebook.com/hung.one.oh.one/

_Github: https://github.com/h-oneohone

Experience

Sun* Vietnam

Al Engineer

January 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Hà Nôi, Việt Nam

PTIT IEC

Al Engineer

April 2022 - January 2024 (1 year 10 months)

Hà Nôi, Việt Nam

Research and develop Al-integrated software to solve problems

Công ty TNHH IOTLink

Intern

March 2023 - December 2023 (10 months)

Hà Nôi, Việt Nam

MotionsCloud

Intern

November 2021 - April 2022 (6 months) Vietnam

Education

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Bachelor Degree, Computer Science · (August 2020 - February 2024)